const easyQuestions=[
    
        {   id:1,
            question: "What is 2 + 2?",
            answer: 4,
        },
        {   id:2,
            question: "What is 5 - 3?",
            answer: 2,
        },
        {    id:3,
            question: "What is 10 / 2?",
            answer: 5,
        },
        
        {   id:4,
            question: "What is 9 + 9?",
            answer: 18,
        },
        {   id:5,
            question: "What is 9 - 3?",
            answer: 6,
        },
        {    id:6,
            question: "What is 4 / 2?",
            answer: 2,
        },
        
        {   id:7,
            question: "What is 12 + 2?",
            answer: 14,
        },
        {   id:8,
            question: "What is 10 - 3?",
            answer: 7,
        },
        {    id:9,
            question: "What is 8 / 2?",
            answer: 4,
        },
        {    id:10,
            question: "What is 9 / 3?",
            answer: 3,
        },
];export default easyQuestions;